He should be here by now.
Reporting.
Wu Dazhou.
I didn't expect
the Army to deploy such an elite unit
to reinforce the Blue Force.
Yuanshan,
his mission
is to take out the Red Force's
two new-type battalions.
Reporting, sir.
I've fought against Hurricane Battalion
and Wind Rider Battalion's commanders
before.
I know them very well.
You can issue your orders directly, sir.
Don't brag.
I've already set the trap for you.
Now,
it's time for your show.
Understood.
Whatever it takes, you must find out
if this unit
is actually the Wind Rider Battalion.
Yes, sir.
Excellent.
Brigade Commander,
Hurricane Battalion's recon detachment
just obtained some intel.
The Blue Force command post
is stationed in a factory in Dingge Zhen.
Is the intel accurate?
Absolutely accurate.
Liu Wangyuan sent it from near the site.
Our scouts
managed to snap a photo of
the enemy commanders.
Although it's a bit blurry,
we can be absolutely certain
it's Di Yunfeng and Long Yuanshan.
This Liu Wangyuan...
Not bad at all.
Give the recon detachment a commendation.
Yes, sir.
Has Jiang Shengqiang made a move?
I'm guessing right as we speak,
the long-range artillery
has already covered the target.
I didn't expect
the Blue Force command post
to actually be in Dingge Zhen.
They dared to use their real command post
as bait.
This Di Yunfeng
is being a bit too overconfident.
Di Yunfeng is unpredictable.
Because of what happened to the 5th Battalion,
even I felt
that it was a
trap to lure our forces in.
This whole situation...
probably isn't that simple.
This Di Yunfeng
sure is crafty.
This battle has turned into a spy drama.
In war,
make the real seem false,
and the false seem real.
This Blue Force commander
really lives up to his reputation.
Battalion Commander.
Long-range fire suppression,
precision missile guidance,
and coordinated drone strikes.
Decapitation Operation
is a complete success.
Confirm the strike results.
Judging from the drone footage,
the strike was effective.
Good.
Notify Staff Officer Liu.
Give him a company,
along with attached detachments,
to mop up the remaining Blue Force there.
Yes, sir.
Something's wrong.
It's an ambush!
Fall back!
Wu Dazhou.
The message has been sent.
Just wait for Guo Zijian to deal with you.
Report.
Speak.
Staff Officer Liu sent back a message.
The target in Dingge Zhen is a decoy.
They were ambushed
by Wu Dazhou's special ops team.
Liu did a great job.
It was my misjudgment.
This Di Yunfeng is simply too cunning.
After all that,
the command post turned out to be a trap.
Strike ineffective.
How is that possible?
Exercise Control doesn't make mistakes.
They exploited a time gap.
There's only one explanation.
He and Long Yuanshan showed themselves
just to put on a show for us.
They waited for our scouts to confirm
before casually leaving,
leaving Wu Dazhou behind
to slaughter the baited prey.
In other words,
our scouts
were under their control from the very beginning.
From the very beginning,
we were being monitored by them.
We still fell for their trap.
But Liu's appearance
can at least provide them with some Reassurance.
Making them believe
that we are the Wind Rider Battalion.
If that's the case,
then the main operational plan
can continue to advance.
But we've lost quite a few troops now.
Furthermore,
they've completely locked down this area.
We must break out.
Don't panic.
Wait until after midnight,
move toward the sea and camouflage.
Await the Brigade Commander's orders.
Yes, sir.
This way,
Jiang Shengqiang's firepower deployment
and actual strength
have basically been exposed.
So what do we do now?
Given the Blue Force's massive firepower,
this time,
it's bound to be a
joint annihilation operation against us.
Pass on my orders.
Order the artillery battalion,
after nightfall,
to immediately set up artillery positions
two kilometers east of our current location,
in an irregular, dispersed formation.
Order the engineer battalion,
after nightfall,
to immediately begin setting up obstacles
and be prepared
to breach obstacles at any time.
Order the reconnaissance battalion
to conduct a full-scale search
for the Blue Force's main body.
They can break formation if necessary.
Also,
for the combat detachments
that have regrouped and assembled,
upon receiving the order,
head to the Phoenix Cry Mountain area.
Yes, sir.
Old Xu,
I suggest
deploying Wind Rider Battalion at once,
with Sky Eye providing strike support.
It's time.
Yes.
In this round,
you could say the Red Force used Sky Eye
to catch the Blue Force off guard.
However,
their own losses are still severe.
Currently, the Blue Force's combatants
basically maintain
a reinforced regiment's
operational strength.
Furthermore,
their special ops unit
is still fully intact.
The Red Force
is in deep trouble.
Although our numbers fall short of the Blue Force,
my Wind Rider Battalion
hasn't even taken the field yet.
And they are equipped with new gear.
They are
worth ten men each.
Report!
Wu Dazhou pulled it off.
Yuanshan,
take a look at this.
Should our exercise this time
be brought to an early end?
But their effective forces
haven't been wiped out yet.
Wind Rider Battalion's operations officer
has already been
gloriously eliminated by Wu Dazhou.
Wind Rider Battalion's remaining troops
have been pushed to the coast by our special ops.
If they make even the slightest move,
I can wipe them out completely.
What else is there for you to worry about?
I suggest
using satellites and drones
over hundreds of square kilometers here
to conduct a comprehensive search.
Are you saying
he'll have a surprise force
descend from the sky?
Without seeing with my own eyes
that brat Guo Zijian show up,
I won't jump to any conclusions.
Guo Zijian again.
Comrades,
from this moment on,
we are reactivated.
Due to the special circumstances,
subsequent orders
will be transmitted via Secure Channel GP-Y.
The current situation is that
Blue Force retains a reinforced regiment,
fully equipped and well-deployed.
After suffering heavy blows,
besides us, the 396th Brigade
only has its headquarters left,
along with some fragmented units.
In short,
the situation is grim.
The 396th Brigade is counting on us.
Some comrades might ask,
where is Hurricane Battalion?
Let me tell you.
Currently, Hurricane Battalion
is down to half a battalion's strength,
and they are all trapped.
Battalion Commander Jiang and his Hurricane Battalion,
from the moment they left the base,
have posed as our Wind Rider Battalion.
Even after taking hits,
their communications
used Wind Rider Battalion's call signs.
Why do you think that is?
It is to cover Wind Rider Battalion
to deal a fatal blow to the Blue Force.
Exactly.
For the sake of a greater victory,
Battalion Commander Jiang and Hurricane Battalion
willingly sacrificed their own honor
to clear minefields and take bullets for us.
This kind of brotherhood and selflessness
makes me, Guo Zijian, truly humbled.
If we fail to win this battle,
we'd let down Battalion Commander Jiang
and Hurricane Battalion's sacrifices.
Comrades,
as a people's army,
if we cannot win battles,
it means the fall of our homeland
and the suffering of our people.
It would also be a disgrace
that our troops can never wash away.
Now, I order:
Air Assault Unit,
split into two forces to night-raid the Blue Force airport
and artillery positions.
Yes, sir!
Long-Range Artillery Unit,
target the Blue Force Special Ops platoon
at the Dingge Zhen fertilizer plant,
with intermittent artillery fire.
Yes, sir!
Drone Formation,
target Blue Force armor at Huangmei Ridge,
and precision-strike Wasp Slope artillery.
Yes, sir!
All combat teams, split into three routes.
Accompanied by recon and early-warning forces,
with full drone surveillance.
One route goes to the fertilizer plant in Dingge Zhen
to eliminate Wu Dazhou's remnants.
One route heads to Huangmei Ridge.
The last route heads to
suspected command post at Sea Breeze Pass.
Engage the enemy according to the combat plan.
Special Ops Platoon!
Here!
Based on earlier recon,
the only ambush spot for Cheetah Commando
is Eagle Beak Canyon.
First Combat Team of the Special Ops Platoon,
take a helicopter
and arrive there in advance.
Second and Third Teams, spread out to escort the infantry.
Yes, sir!
Staff Officer Liang leads the Electronic Warfare Detachment.
Comrades,
during the early preparations,
we entered a closed hibernation,
keeping even the Exercise Control personnel in the dark.
Now, the control personnel for all units are in position.
Everything is ready.
I order,
all personnel of Wind Rider Battalion,
move out!
Yes, sir!
Old Qiao,
see that?
With the battle at this stage,
the curtain on the future battlefield has lifted.
Soon,
Guo Zijian's joint operations chess game
will be laid out before Di Yunfeng.
This is a typical prototype of all-domain operations.
Information warfare will be more absolute.
It's just a single battalion.
The disparity in strength is too great.
Guo Zijian...
Guo Zijian might not be able to turn the tables.
As modern technology permeates everything,
the scale of future battlefields
is no longer classified
by personnel and equipment quantities.
Those were your words.
You're using my own words against me.
Zhang,
I remember back then,
you weren't very optimistic about the Wind Rider Battalion.
Oh, you.
Judging from the current
few small-scale localized battles around the world,
expanding battalion-level capabilities
has already become a trend.
This is not only seen
in countries that aren't military powers,
but even
major powers with superior militaries
are actively implementing it.
This time,
I fully trust Wind Rider Battalion and Guo Zijian.
All set and ready.
We will accomplish the mission.
On my command.
Stand by to move out.
Lin Yihu!
Here!
First Squad, prepare to assemble.
Yes, sir!
Battalion Commander.
Didn't get any sleep?
Can't sleep.
Before we cut all outside contact,
we sent out two messages.
One was to the brigade command post,
and the other to the Wind Rider Battalion.
Now it seems
neither of them
worked.
Tell me your thoughts.
The search perimeter is closing in on the alert zone.
It seems
at daybreak,
the charade
will be exposed.
Be patient.
Sometimes,
waiting quietly
also reflects a unit's discipline.
Captain.
It's so late.
Why'd Brigade Commander order a sweep?
Delays are dangerous.
Right now, our troop strength and firepower
far exceed theirs.
As long as we catch their men,
they will undoubtedly lose.
Do you think the Brigade Commander
is also having doubts?
Doubts about what?
The Brigade Commander's assurance
and confidence in us
all stem from
our ability to execute commands precisely.
He just doesn't want to drag this out.
Right.
Concentrate our firepower
and end the battle at once.
Reporting, Battalion Commander.
The enemy search team has entered the forward positions.
Requesting orders.
Can you wipe out the enemy without opening fire?
They must be special forces.
They won't be easy to deal with.
Once your position is exposed,
eliminate the enemy on the spot.
All personnel, abandon your current positions
and relocate to new hiding spots immediately.
Yes, sir.
Rewind the video a bit.
Play it from here.
Fall in!
Emergency assembly!
Don't get cocky.
Even though we've been taken out,
you've exposed yourselves too.
None of you will get away.
Is that so?
The rest of the Red Army's main force has been located.
But once they open fire,
他们'll relocate immediately.
Our follow-up forces have caught up.
They won't get away.
Now it's all up to us.
Where did those planes come from?
Did our fighters get the intel too
and go in for a bombing run?
Impossible.
The intel is point-to-point.
I haven't even reported it yet.
It's the Red Army!
Take cover!
Report!
Combat report received.
The Blue Force Special Ops camp
is under full fire from Wind Rider Battalion.
Infantry units
are expected to arrive at the camp soon
to clear the battlefield.
We're liberated.
Good.
Guo Zijian didn't let me down.
Orders.
Launch a full assault
and wipe out all Blue Force search teams.
Send a message to Wind Rider Battalion.
Tell them to watch out for
the Blue Force's Cheetah Commando.
A lot of our equipment
was destroyed by those brats.
Yes, sir.
Guo Zijian,
it's time to show your true skills.
Report.
Our Special Ops camp in Dingge Zhen
is under multi-wave Red Force air strikes.
Personnel narrowly survived,
but equipment suffered heavy losses.
Where is this firepower coming from?
Could it be Xu Lingjun's second echelon?
No need to guess.
It must be Guo Zijian's Wind Rider Battalion.
Sir.
The armored positions at Huangmei Ridge
and the artillery in Wild Bee Valley
are under saturation drone strikes.
Their combat loss rates have reached
60% and 65%, respectively.
Pass on my orders.
All long-range equipment in our unit
must go on full combat alert.
Yes, sir.
Order
the reconnaissance and early warning detachment
to locate the source of Red Army's fire.
Yes, sir.
Report.
Go ahead.
Reconnaissance shows
that three Red Army infantry units
are advancing via Haicheng County and Dingmei County.
They are 60 kilometers away.
Due to darkness, their equipment is unknown.
After attacking from the sky,
they sweep the ground.
Looks like they're trying to wipe us out.
He's dreaming.
It's time for my Cheetah Commando
to show what they're made of.
Pass on my order.
Our infantry units
must at all costs
delay the Red Army convoy's advance.
Furthermore,
order Tian Kang
to set up an ambush at Eagle Beak Canyon.
An ambush at Eagle Beak Canyon.
Tell him
to wipe out the Red Army special ops unit.
Don't let a single soldier escape.
Otherwise,
tell him never to see me again.
Yes, sir!
Eagle Beak Canyon is indeed a good place for an ambush.
I just wonder if we can actually
get a bite of this juicy meat.
I, Di Yunfeng,
love eating meat the most.
With meat brought right to my mouth,
there's no reason to turn it down.
Excellent.
The appearance of the Wind Rider Battalion
is meant to catch them off guard,
strike back,
and deliver a fatal blow.
A fatal blow?
We're nowhere near that.
The Red Army only took out
the Blue Army's long-range firepower,
crippled their armor and artillery,
and destroyed Blue Army special ops' gear.
But the Blue Army's proud Cheetah Commando
remains completely unscathed.
Old Commander,
even though you've been out of the army for years,
your military expertise
hasn't diminished one bit.
You have a clear grasp of the battlefield.
You flatter me.
However, you don't know our battalion commander.
He
always manages to surprise us.
Just you wait and see.
Indeed.
It seems I really don't know him well enough.
Captain.
Under infrared conditions,
the precision kill rate has reached 60%.
That's already very high.
As for any remaining equipment and personnel,
Team Three will finish them off.
Good. Prepare to relocate.
Yes, sir.
Comrades,
based on the latest intel from command,
Eagle Beak Canyon isn't the only ambush.
We are adjusting the mission as follows.
Ma Zhengzheng,
you'll handle close-quarters combat.
Zhao Xiaoyun,
you will lead Team One.
Once you reach the south slope,
use night vision gear
and silent night-vision drones for support
to remotely command the special ops,
and eliminate nearby enemies.
Snipers,
secure the high ground on the left.
Focus on taking out any stragglers.
Is that clear?
Clear!
Move out!
Team One, follow me!
Team Two, follow me! Target: north slope.
Attention, Cheetah spotted.
Prepare to close the net.
Targeted elimination.
Reporting. Unit One has reached the designated area.
Over.
Reporting.
Unit Two has reached the designated area.
Over.
Communications.
02, 02.
This is 702.
Do you copy? Do you copy?
Copy.
702, this is 02.
Go ahead.
Enemy spotted. Halt advance.
Attention all units.
Convoy, halt advance.
Halt advance.
Reporting to Cheetah.
Red force vehicles have halted.
Recon vehicles advancing to check. Over.
Understood.
Team 1, Team 2, get ready.
Once you find a spot,
take cover immediately.
He won't dare shoot.
Team 1, Team 2,
respond if you copy.
We've been ambushed.
What do we do now?
The enemy on the hillside
won't be able to get down anytime soon.
Wait for my command.
Target this Red Army recon team now,
and launch an ambush,
and cover my ambush squad
as they charge into the enemy convoy
to ambush their combat vehicles up close.
Yes, sir.
Intercept vehicles
Equipment
Sorry, I hit a bit too hard.
You've lost. Withdraw from the exercise.
To tell you the truth,
in my entire career from lieutenant to major,
I've never suffered such a huge loss before.
Only you could pull this off,
or this command vehicle wouldn't be destroyed.
My combat losses are negligible.
Anyway, once past Eagle Beak Canyon,
the two combat teams will split up.
They each have their own commanders.
My mission is already complete.
Dad.
Did you see that?
That's our Godspeed Morph
exoskeleton equipment.
It's not only extremely lightweight
and highly durable,
but it also provides great jumping power.
It boosts a soldier's speed and payload
by 20 percent.
Yang Maolin
is giving us a massive advertisement.
If the exercise is a success,
I'll give you major credit.
You mean us.
This is the exoskeleton equipment
designed by Military Dream Group, right?
Tonight has truly been an eye-opener.
As for the exoskeletons,
this is just the beginning.
The best is yet to come.
When I saw Tian Kang earlier,
in a chokehold by Red Army special forces...
To be honest,
it was hard to watch.
Sir,
you need to remain impartial.
It's not that I'm being unfair.
You know,
Tian Kang and his Cheetah Commando
were a model unit we established.
But I never expected that overnight,
Guo Zijian's troops would wipe them out.
I'm just lamenting
how the current speed of technological progress
can turn the honors we just earned
instantly
into history.
Can I ask you guys a question?
Go ahead.
Are you guys
the real Wind Rider Battalion?
Wind Rider Battalion.
The real deal.
All teams, move out.
I didn't expect
they'd beat us to it
and ambush us at Eagle Beak Canyon.
This kid is really something.
He wiped out my entire Cheetah unit.
We were overconfident in the Cheetahs.
An opponent like Guo Zijian
always exceeds my expectations.
He thinks
using this tactic
will win him this war.
He's being too naive.
Yuanshan,
I have a favor
to ask of you.
And you're the only one I can turn to.
Brigade Commander Di.
According to the mission,
I am now your staff officer.
Just give the order.
Well done.
Where is Guo Zijian now?
Heading to the main battlefield.
Good, tell him
I'll say it again.
Regarding Wind Rider Battalion's command,
no interference, no overriding.
Understood.
Now, through Sky Eye
and other intel channels, we've concluded
that Sea Breeze Pass is the Blue Force's nerve center.
We can launch the final assault now.
The Commissar is right.
Chief of Staff,
hurry up and gather our men.
Also, notify Jiang Shengqiang
to converge at Sea Breeze Pass immediately.
Make one thing clear to Guo Zijian.
He must commit at least two teams,
including the drone squadron,
to support the main force's operation.
But Sky Eye
after providing its last update,
has been jammed.
The information we have
is already enough.
Sir!
The First Team
has reached the fertilizer plant in Dingge Zhen.
But at the scene,
they found no Blue Force commandos.
Then what did we bomb in those waves?
Was our intel wrong?
The intel shouldn't be wrong.
They found a lot of damaged equipment,
but very few casualties.
They asked where the others went,
but got no answers.
Where did they go? Where could they go?
They ran away.
Wu Dazhou led his commando team
just to seek revenge on us.
We can't find them now,
so I'm afraid there will be trouble later.
So, what's your assessment?
It's simple.
This isn't over yet.
And,
relocate the command post.
Yes, sir.
Order.
Order all unit members near Sea Breeze Pass
to quickly fall back near the command post.
Stagger their positions
and set up a tight defense.
Yes, sir.
Brigade Commander,
Currently, Liang Hong's information platform
and our information platform
have both captured the Blue Force command post's signal.
We can confirm it's definitely Di Yunfeng.
Excellent.
They say this Di Yunfeng
has never lost.
This time, let's give him a good taste
of defeat.
If Guo Zijian hadn't planned ahead,
and if Wind Rider Battalion wasn't a new-type battalion,
it's hard to say if we could've turned the tables.
Report!
Jiang Shengqiang and his men have arrived
and are closing in with Dong Zhenguo.
At the same time,
the personnel sent to Huangmei Ridge to clean up,
Team Three of the Wind Rider Battalion,
with a 40 percent casualty rate,
are also rushing to Sea Breeze Pass.
This time, Di Yunfeng,
even if he grew wings,
couldn't fly out of Sea Breeze Pass.
Tell me,
what does everyone think
about the current situation?
As for the operational procedures,
there are no issues.
But looking at this exercise,
I still feel unsatisfied.
It shouldn't end this quickly.
If you ask me,
I'd sum it up like this:
Each with their own hidden agenda.
After running exercises for years,
everyone has gotten smart.
So no one is willing to risk it all.
That is complete nonsense.
Sir,
we've all had our say.
Whatever tricks you have up your sleeve,
why don't you show us?
My answer is...
The mantis stalks the cicada,
unaware of the oriole behind.
Whoever can become
the one with the slingshot behind the oriole
will likely be the one
to have the last laugh.
Sir.
When two armies face off,
there is only the mantis and the cicada.
How could a third-party oriole appear,
let alone a fourth party with a slingshot?
The beauty of strategic thinking
lies exactly in this.
Lies exactly in this.
The weather forecast wouldn't be wrong today, right?
Look at this beautiful sunshine.
Report. The cloud movement is correct.
The wind direction is correct.
The wind should pick up around 1700 hours.
I invited you to watch the sunrise.
And you're telling me all this nonsense.
You...